Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1949-2010
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 1: Administrative records, 1949-2007 (Boxes 1-196)
  - Subseries 1.5: Communications and Events, 1950-2006
    - Sub-subseries 1.5.1: Events, 1950s-1998
      - Borders Events - Cleo's Nose, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - British Embassy luncheon invites, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Brochures, letters, and invitations, 1982-1985 (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - Building expansion announcements, circa 1955 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - Career Day, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 11)
      - Career Day information (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      - Career Day information (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 114, Folder 13)
      - Catherine Irwin's farewell, September 13, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 14)
      - Catholic University Angels in America, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 15)
      - City celebration bicentennial, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 16)
      - Colorado College Summer Arts Festival, 1985-1987 (Box 114, Folder 17)
      - Congressional Arts Caucus: Summer and Smoke, March 1993 (Box 114, Folder 18)
      - Corcoran Gallery exhibition, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 19)
      - Dedication Invitations, Kreeger opening, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 1)
      - Doug Wager event, April 1998 (Box 115, Folder 2)
      - Doug Wager farewell event, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 3)
      - Doug Wager farewell (1 of 2), April 1998 (Box 115, Folder 4)
      - Doug Wager farewell (2 of 2), April 1998 (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - Employee recognition, 1994-1996 (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - Employee recognition, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 7)
      - Event committee calendars/budgets, notes, memos, 1991-1992 (Box 115, Folder 8)
      - Event program: Hebrew Academy of Washington, May 12, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 9)
      - Farewell to Zelda Fichandler, March 20, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 10)
      - First Lady Benefit, March 16, 1998 (Box 115, Folder 11)
      - George Furth visit, 1989 (Box 115, Folder 12)
      - Gala opening programs, 1980-1985 (Box 115, Folder 13)
      - Gala prospectus, August 13, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 14)
      - Gelb luncheon, 1995 (Box 115, Folder 15)
      - General bicentennial, 1976-1977, 1974-1975 (Box 115, Folder 16)
      - Guest book sign-in, ground breakings and events, 1968-1972 (Box 115, Folder 17)
      - Gross National Product troupe in residence, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 18)
      - Holiday banners, undated (Box 115, Folder 19)
      - Hong Kong Festival program, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 20)
      - House Arrest premier, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 21)
      - International Theatre Fortnite, Quebec, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 1)
      - I'd Rather be Rich board benefit, March 1994 (Box 116, Folder 2)
      - Impact DC Reception, January 27, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 3)
      - Israel tour, 1986-1987 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      - Invitation releases, 1988-1989 (Box 116, Folder 5)
      - K2 benefit, April 22, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      - Kreeger dedication, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - Kreeger dedication news articles, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - Kreeger theater dedication, November 29, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      - Kreeger dedication program, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      - Love Letters benefit, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 11)
      - Love's metamorphosis symposium, 1990-1991 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      - Memos on Fichandler Stage dedication, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 13)
      - Mid-Atlantic Arts Consortium, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 14)
      - Moscow tour, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 15)
      - NEA/Richard Wilbur tribute, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 16)
      - New building, opening of theater, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      - New building opening, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 2)
      - New Voices for a New America announcement, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      - O'Neill National Playwrights Conference, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - Open House, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 5)
      - Open House, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 6)
      - Open House, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 7)
      - Opening night and open invitations, 1965-1966 (Box 117, Folder 8)
      - Phillip Morris event, 1993-1994 (Box 117, Folder 9)
      - Phillip Morris, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      - Press coverage of grants/fundraising, 1950s-1984 (Box 117, Folder 11)
      - Press luncheon, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 12)
      - Press luncheon, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 13)
      - Press night/opening night invitations, early 1990s (Box 117, Folder 14)
      - Press night invitations, 1994-1995 (Box 117, Folder 15)
      - Remy night at Arena Stage, 1988-1989 (Box 117, Folder 16)
      - Remy Night "On the Town", 1989 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - Reopening of Arena Stage news article, 1957 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Retreat at Lowes, August 26, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - "A Room of One's Own" Post-show reception, 1994 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - Rose Robison Cowen Acting Fellowship fund, 1989-1994 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Ruling class opening, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Russian Tour card and button, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Season benefit, 1980-1981 (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - Second annual arts caucus event, March 3, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - She Stoops to Conquer opening, Zelda Fichandler, March 20, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 10)
      - Silent Auction (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 118, Folder 11)
      - Silent Auction (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 118, Folder 12)
      - Soviet publication - America, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      - Soviet Tour, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      - Special events, fundraising, 1970s-1980s (Box 118, Folder 15)
      - Spring benefit - invitation designs, 1987-1988 (Box 118, Folder 16)
      - State of the Arts in the US symposium, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 17)
      - St. Cecelia's Academy, 1970-1971 (Box 118, Folder 18)
      - Bill Steward Stamp award, 1984-1990 (Box 119, Folder 1)
      - Stratford Festival, 1976 (Box 119, Folder 2)
      - Symposium details - "I Am a Man", 1994-1995 (Box 119, Folder 3)
      - Tea with Miss Manners, October 1992 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      - THIS group tour, 1995 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      - Total Beverage fund raiser, 1994 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      - Two Gentlemen of Verona cast party, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      - Two Gents Event/National Woman's Party, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      - Waiting Room parties, 1995 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      - A Walk in the Woods symposium, June 1989 (Box 119, Folder 10)
      - Waterfront metro station opening, 1988-1992 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      - "Win with Wintergreen" buttons (from Of Thee I Sing), 1992 (Box 119, Folder 12)
      - World Theatre Festival, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 13)
      - World Theatre Festival, 1973-1976 (Box 119, Folder 14)
      - Yuri Lyubimov lunch at NYU, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Sub-subseries 1.5.2: Communications and Marketing, 1950s-1997
      Sub-subseries 2: Communications and Marketing includes records produced by the Communications and Marketing departments.
      - 1983-84 Benefit, 1983-1984 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - 50s press photo: new Arena Stage Model with Zelda Fichandler, circa 1950s (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - Anna Deavere Smith residency publicity, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 3)
      - Arena Stage premieres/history, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 4)
      - Audience polls, news articles, 1967, 1971 (Box 120, Folder 5)
      - Audience surveys, 1963-1964 (Box 120, Folder 6)
      - Audience surveys, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      - Bibliography of publications about/mentioning Arena Stage, 1970s (Box 120, Folder 8)
      - Building and show research/publicity, 1965-1974 (Box 120, Folder 9)
      - Class C Trial in Yokohama research, 1984 (Box 120, Folder 10)
      - Communications - Arena and Russia, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 11)
      - Communications board committee meeting, May 15, 1997 (Box 120, Folder 12)
      - Communications - Budget files, 1992-1993 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Communication - Budget and JE and general ledger, 1993-1994 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      - Communications committee, 1990-1991 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      - Communications committee, 1991-1992 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      - Communications committee, 1991-1993 (Box 121, Folder 5)
      - Communications committee materials, 1993-1994 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - Communications committee - August 27 co-chairs meeting, October 1 meeting, 1992 (Box 121, Folder 7)
      - Communications committee, November 1992 (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - Communications committee, February 1993 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      - Communications committee, April-June 1993 (Box 121, Folder 10)
      - Communications committee meeting, September 1993 (Box 121, Folder 11)
      - Communications committee meeting, November 1993 (Box 121, Folder 12)
      - Communications committee meeting, March 1994 (Box 121, Folder 13)
      - Communications committee, March-April 1994 (Box 121, Folder 14)
      - Communications committee meeting, November 1994 (Box 121, Folder 15)
      - Communications committee meeting, December 1994 (Box 121, Folder 16)
      - Communications committee meeting, January 1995 (Box 121, Folder 17)
      - Communications committee meeting - Shugoll research, May 1995 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - Communications committee meeting, October 1995 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - Communications committee, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Communications committee meeting, January 1996 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Communications committee, 1996-1997 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - Communications committee meeting, 1996-1997 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Communications/Development bi-weekly meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - Communications - guide listing budget, 1993-1994 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Communications - guide listing budget, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - Communications - guide listing budget, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      - Communications - Income goals per-show, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 11)
      - Communications income projection and goals, 1996-1997 (Box 122, Folder 12)
      - Communications - Interdepartmental minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 13)
      - Communications - Interdepartmental staff meeting minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 14)
      - Communications-marketing meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 122, Folder 15)
      - Communications-marketing minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 122, Folder 16)
      - Communications-marketing meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 17)
      - Communications and marketing department meetings, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 18)
      - Communications - marketing minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 19)
      - Communications-marketing meeting minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 122, Folder 20)
      - Communications and marketing department meetings, March-April 1995 (Box 122, Folder 21)
      - Communications-marketing goals meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 22)
      - Communications meeting minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 122, Folder 23)
      - Communications meeting minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 122, Folder 24)
      - Communications - meetings, 95-96 season, information requests, 1995-1996 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - Communications meeting plan presentation, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - Communications staff minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - Communications staff meeting minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - Newspaper reviews, guides, and magazines, 1968-1978 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - Fires Flyer distribution, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - Growth through innovation: The 1995-96 communications plan (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - I Am a Man press night, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - Long-range plan, 1994, 1992-1997 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - Long range plan 1992-1997 draft, 1982-1983 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      - Monteith and Rand, 1991-1992 (Box 123, Folder 11)
      - New voices for a new America, 1993-1994 (Box 123, Folder 12)
      - Opening night invites, 1993-1994 (Box 123, Folder 13)
      - Playquest background, June 29, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 14)
      - ProTix LP, 1969-1970 (Box 123, Folder 15)
      - Public relations correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 123, Folder 16)
      - Resolution I-283 to honor Arena Stage and other letters of thanks, 1961-1980 (Box 123, Folder 17)
      - Rubenstein graphic endowment, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 18)
      - Rubenstein graphic endowment - Animal Crackers - Robert Rauschenberg, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 19)
      - Rubenstein graphic endowment - Buried Child - Ralph Goings, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 20)
      - Rubenstein graphic endowment - Happy End - Larry Rivers, 1983-1984 (Box 123, Folder 21)
      - Rubenstein graphics: Jasper Johns, Fall 1986 (Box 123, Folder 22)
      - Rubenstein graphics endowment: Robert Longo, Fall 1986 (Box 123, Folder 23)
      - Silent auction items, 1995-1996 (Box 123, Folder 24)
      - Subscriber focus groups, 1994-1995 (Box 123, Folder 25)
      - Theater as a Career, Late 1960s (Box 123, Folder 26)
      - Zelda's resignation information, 1990 (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - Sub-subseries 1.5.3: Printed material, 1950-2006
      Sub-subseries 3: Printed material includes subscriber materials, mailings, brochures, reviews collected and arranged by play title, and programs organized chronologically.
      - Advertisements, 1954-1955 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - Advertisements, 1957-1958 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - Advertisements, 1958-1959 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - Advertisements, 1960-1961 (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - Advertisements, 1960-1962 (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - Advertisements, 1960-1965 (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - Advertisements, 1962-1963 (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - Advertisements (1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - Advertisements (2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - Advertisements, 1965-1966 (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - Advertisements (1 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - Advertisements (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Advertisements, 1967-1969 (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - Advertisements, 1968-1969 (Box 125, Folder 7)
      - Advertisements, 1969-1970 (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - Advertisements, 1970-1971 (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - Advertisements, 1971-1972 (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - Advertisements, 1972-1973 (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - Advertisements, 1973-1974 (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - Advertisements, 1975-1976 (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - Advertisements, Summer 1976 (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - Advertisements, ABC, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - Advertisements, Oba Koso, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - Advertisements - Playtime, 1963-1964 (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - Advertisements - Playtime, 1975-1976 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - Advertisements - Post/Star, 1976-1977 (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - Advertisements - Stage Directory, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - Advertisements, Star/News, 1972 (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - Advertisements, tearsheet files, 1977-1978 (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - Advertisements, This Week, 1963-1964 (Box 127, Folder 11)
      - Advertisements - Tom's Picture Ads for 1967-1968 subscription drive (Box 127, Folder 12)
      - Advertisements - The Washington Post, December 1, 1976-June 10, 1978 (Box 127, Folder 13)
      - Advertisements - Washington Star and Post, 1972-1973 (Box 127, Folder 14)
      - Advertisements - The Washington Star, November 7 1976-June 26, 1977 (Box 127, Folder 15)
      - Advertisement in the Vagabond Players playbill, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 16)
      - "After the Fall" articles, 1980 (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - Allen Lee Hughes Fellow Program and Intern mailings, circa 1990s (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - America's Arena, 1982-1985 (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - America's Arena, 1986-1987 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - America's Arena, 1987-1990 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - America's Arena and Saturday Review, 1971-1983 (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - American Theatre and Guide to the Arts, April 1985, May 1978 (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - "The American Theatre" and holiday card, 1969-1970 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - Anniversary and Subscription Drive, 1963-1964 (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - Announcing the New Arena Stage Congressional Ticket Hotline, 1990 (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - Annual reports, 1981-1989 (Box 128, Folder 11)
      - Arena Stage Angels newsletters, mailings, 1985-1986 (Box 128, Folder 12)
      - "The Arena Arrow" newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 128, Folder 13)
      - "Arena Arrow", 1990-1991 (Box 128, Folder 14)
      - "The Arena Link" newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 128, Folder 15)
      - Articles on other theatres around the world, 1972-1973 (Box 128, Folder 16)
      - Arena Stage Associates Listing Insert - 1940s Radio Hour program, 1978 (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Arena Stage Associates mailings, circa 1980 (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - Arena Stage Associates mailings, brochures, invitations, 1983-1984 (Box 129, Folder 3)
      - Associates mailings, development invitations, 1985-1986 (Box 129, Folder 4)
      - Arena Stage Associates material, 1960s-1980s (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - Arena Stage Associates - Winter's Tale insert, 1979 (Box 129, Folder 6)
      - Associates telegram, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 7)
      - Arena Stage History, 1976-1982 (Box 129, Folder 8)
      - Audio described series, 2001-2002 (Box 129, Folder 9)
      - Audio described series, sign interpreted series mailings, 2003-2004 (Box 129, Folder 10)
      - Box layout, book I, printed materials, 1985-1986 (Box 129, Folder 11)
      - Box office forms, mailings, 1979-1980 (Box 129, Folder 12)
      - Brochures, 1980s-1990s (Box 129, Folder 13)
      - Brochures, chronology, early programs, 1961-1980s (Box 129, Folder 14)
      - Brochures, invitations, mailers, form letters, 1986-1987 (Box 129, Folder 15)
      - Brochures, invitations, mailers, form letters, 1986-1987 (Box 129, Folder 16)
      - Brochures, mailers, 1976-1977 (Box 129, Folder 17)
      - Brochures, mailings, invitations, 1976-1980 (Box 129, Folder 18)
      - Brochures, mailings, promotional materials, 1985-1986 (Box 129, Folder 19)
      - Brochures, mailings, 1989-1991 (Box 129, Folder 20)
      - Brochures, mailings, programs, 1993-1995 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Brochures, season schedules, 1984-1987 (Box 130, Folder 2)
      - Brochures - Sign interpreted series, 1988-2001 (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - Bumper sticker, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 4)
      - Calendar, 1986 (Box 130, Folder 5)
      - Calendar: The Washington Star, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 6)
      - Callboard, Arena Associates newsletter, 1973-1979 (Box 130, Folder 7)
      - Callboard and the Arena Link, 1975-1980 (Box 130, Folder 8)
      - Callboard - Arena Associates and GWU Alumni Review, 1961-1977 (Box 130, Folder 9)
      - Capital Comment, September 1967 (Box 130, Folder 10)
      - Community Carol mailings, community relations materials, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 11)
      - Construction/theatre reviews, 1950; 1961 (Box 130, Folder 12)
      - Contents list, printed press box 2, 1984-1985 (Box 130, Folder 13)
      - Contents map, box 1, 1985-1986 (Box 130, Folder 14)
      - Critical overview and 1978 fall brochure (Box 130, Folder 15)
      - Critical overview, promotional material, 1978-1979 (Box 130, Folder 16)
      - The Cultural Climate, circa 1970s (Box 130, Folder 17)
      - David Chambers's letter to subscribers and season schedule flyer, 1978-1979 (Box 130, Folder 18)
      - Development and communications, mailers, subscriptions, 1991-1992 (Box 130, Folder 19)
      - Development, fundraising, subscriber mailings, 1961-1982 (Box 130, Folder 20)
      - Development mailings, article copies, 1980-1992 (Box 130, Folder 21)
      - Development mailings, 1979-1980 (Box 130, Folder 22)
      - Development and marketing mailings, brochures, invitations, 1979-1981 (Box 130, Folder 23)
      - Development and marketing mailings, brochures, pamphlets, 1980-1982 (Box 131, Folder 1)
      - Development and marketing mailings and brochures, playbills, 1982-1984 (Box 131, Folder 2)
      - Development and marketing mailings, pamphlets, brochures, 1982-1989 (Box 131, Folder 3)
      - Development and marketing mailings, brochures, pamphlets, 1984-1989 (Box 131, Folder 4)
      - Development and marketing mailings, brochures, pamphlets, 1986-1989 (Box 131, Folder 5)
      - Development pieces, mailings, 1986-1987 (Box 131, Folder 6)
      - Development/special events invitations and mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 131, Folder 7)
      - Early brochures (1 of 2), 1951-1971 (Box 131, Folder 8)
      - Early brochures (2 of 2), 1951-1971 (Box 131, Folder 9)
      - Eat, Drink, and Be Merry for Arena/Letter and Return cards, 1980 (Box 131, Folder 10)
      - 1966 Excellent Design Awards (Box 131, Folder 11)
      - "Expect the Unexpected" letter/brochure, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 12)
      - Exxon-sponsored opening night materials, 1981 (Box 131, Folder 13)
      - Fact sheets, publicity for Arena Stage building, 1970-1981 (Box 131, Folder 14)
      - "First Preview" issues, group sales mailings, 1984-1985 (Box 131, Folder 15)
      - "First Preview" and other group sales mailings, 1985-1986 (Box 131, Folder 16)
      - First Preview newsletter, 1985-1987 (Box 132, Folder 1)
      - Flyers, 1957-1973 (Box 132, Folder 2)
      - Flyers, 1986-1987 (Box 132, Folder 3)
      - Flyers and inserts, 1977-1978 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - Flyers, invitations, subscriber materials, 1984-1986 (Box 132, Folder 5)
      - Flyers and pamphlets, 1973-1974 (Box 132, Folder 6)
      - Foreign press, 1960s (Box 132, Folder 7)
      - Foreign press - French, Polish, Spanish, German, 1963-1972 (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - Form letters (Richard Bryant), 1982-1983 (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - Founding member mailings and other promotional material, 1985-1986 (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - Fund raising brochures, mailings, 1980s-1990s (Box 132, Folder 11)
      - Fund raising information, November 1978 (Box 132, Folder 12)
      - Fund run, 1979 (Box 132, Folder 13)
      - Gala/Development/Associate mailings, 1984-1985 (Box 132, Folder 14)
      - General information and miscellaneous pieces, brochures, mailings, 1986-1987 (Box 132, Folder 15)
      - Giant Food associates night for the Winter's Tale, circa late 1970s-early 1980s (Box 132, Folder 16)
      - Golden Circle and student subscription series, 1979-1980 (Box 132, Folder 17)
      - Group sales/audience development mailings and brochures, 1987-1988 (Box 132, Folder 18)
      - Group sales/first previews, 1986-1987 (Box 132, Folder 19)
      - Group sales mailings, 1979-1980 (Box 132, Folder 20)
      - Group sales promotional material, 1982-1983 (Box 132, Folder 21)
      - Group sales stationery and Teibele ASA listing, 1979 (Box 132, Folder 22)
      - Growth From Within brochure, late 1960s (Box 132, Folder 23)
      - H.E. Oliver Wright - British Ambassador press information, 1982-1983 (Box 132, Folder 24)
      - House management mailing, 1979-1980 (Box 132, Folder 25)
      - Individual production flyers, 1960s-1980s (Box 132, Folder 26)
      - Invitations, 1986-1987 (Box 132, Folder 27)
      - Invitations, 1986-1987 (Box 132, Folder 28)
      - Invitations, 1987-1988 (Box 132, Folder 29)
      - Invitations, 1989-1990s (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - Invitations, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Invitations, brochures, and letters, 1968-1977 (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Invitations/mailings, 1990-1991 (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - Invitations, mailings, promotional material, 1983-1984 (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - Invitations to press and opening nights, 1984-1985 (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Invitations, promotional materials, mailings, annual report, 1981-1982 (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Invites and time notes, 1978-1980 (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - Journal advertisements, 1994-1995 (Box 133, Folder 9)
      - Kathak dancers of North India, other South Asian classical dancers, 1950s-1960s (Box 133, Folder 10)
      - Letterhead, program for printing, 1979-1980 (Box 133, Folder 11)
      - Magazines, 1990, 1997 (Box 133, Folder 12)
      - Magazine press, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 13)